UNITE International Relations Department Records 6000/027
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- ITGLWF to all Affiliates, 1995-2000 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- ITGLWF - Correspondence with Laura Carter, 1996-2000 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- ITGLWF Correspondence - 2000 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- ITGLWF Correspondence -- 1999 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- ITGLWF Correspondence 1998 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- ITGLWF Correspondence - 1997 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- ITGLWF Correspondence - 1996 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- ITGLWF General Correspondence 1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- ITGLWF Meetings -- 1999/2000 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- ITGLWF 8th World Congress 2000 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- ITGLWF Presidium, Executive Committee & Strategic Approaches Meetings Dakar, Senegal October 1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- ITGLWF Meetings -- 1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- ITGLWF Presidium and Executive Committee Meetings - 1997 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Afghanistan, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Algeria, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Antigua and Barbuda, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Albania, 1998-2001 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Argentina, 1996-2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Australia, 1995-2000 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Armenia, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Austria, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Bangladesh - BIGU, 1995-2000 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Bangladesh, 1996-2000 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Barbados, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Belarus, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Belgium, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Bolivia, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Brazil, 1996-2001 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Burkina Faso, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Burma, 1995-2001 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Bulgaria, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Cambodia [Folder 1 of 2], 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Cambodia [Folder 2 of 2], 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Cameroon, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Canada, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Chile, 1995-2001 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Columbia, 1996-2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Congo, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Costa Rica, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Cuba, 1995-2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Socialist International and Social Democrats, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Civitas/Civitas Panamericano, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Cornell University, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- ORIT, 1995-1999 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- IUF (International Union of Food, Agricultural, Hotel, Restaurant, Catering Tobacco and Allied Workers' Association), 1996 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- National Labor Committee, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Organization of American States (OAS), 1998 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- OECD (Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development), 1995-1999 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- International Rescue Committee (IRC), 1995-1999 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- [Folder 1 of 2], 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- ILO [Folder 2 of 2], 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- ICEM Affiliation Fees, 1998-2001 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- ICEM, 1997-2001 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Human Rights Watch, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIP Convention - Sept. 1997 Pittsburgh, PA (Box 20, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Convention - Oct. 1995 New York (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Friedrich Elbert Stiftung (FES), 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- International Organizing General, 1996-2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Research/Organizing Requests Miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Ditchley Foundation, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Speeches, Studies, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- U.S. Department of Labor, 1996-2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Directories, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Freedom House, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- United Nations, 1995-1998 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Resumes, 1995-1999 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- U.S. Department of State, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Interpreters/Translators, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- United Nations (1997-2000) (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Trilateral Commission, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- UFCW (United Food and Commercial Workers International Union), 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- The Stanley Foundation, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- ICFTU 17th World Conference 2000 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- ICFTU Telex News 1996 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- ICFTU Telex News 1995 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- ICFTU Online 2001 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- ICFTU Online 2000 July - December (Box 20, Folder 23)
- ICFTU Online 2000 January - June (Box 20, Folder 24)
- ICTFU Online 1999 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- ICFTU Online 1998 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- ICFTU Online 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- ICTFU Circulars 2000 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- ICFTU Circulars 1999 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- ICFTU Circulars 1998 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- ICFTU Circulars 1997 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- ICFTU Circulars 1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- ICFTU, 1996-1999 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- ICFTU, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- ICFTU Conference on Globalization, Investment and Labour Standards 1998 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- WTO Campaign 1999 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- ITGLWF Executive Meeting Norkopping Sweden 2000 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- ITGLWF 2000 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- ITGLWF Targeting Multinational Project Company Profits - Vanity Fair, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- ITGLWF Targeting Multinational Project Company Profile: Pou Chan, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- ITGLWF Targeting Multinationals Project Company Profile Daun and CIE AG, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- ITGLWF Targeting Multinationals Project Company Profile: Coats Viyella (Box 21, Folder 17)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Brussels, 11 April 2000 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Brussels 30 April 1999 [Folder 1 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 19)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Brussels, 30 April 1999 [Folder 2 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 20)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting Berlin 7-9 October 1998 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting Dakar, Senegal 27-29 October 1999 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Dekar Senegal, 26 October 1999 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- ICFTU 17th World Congress Durban, South Africa, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- ICFTU, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- ITGLWF Strategic Approaches Subcommittee, 1995-2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- ITGLWF -- International Organizing: Targeting Multinational Companies, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Montreal --- October 1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- 1996 ITGLWF Presidium and Executive Committee Meetings (Box 22, Folder 6)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Geneva - November 3-4, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- ITGLWF Strategic Approaches Committee 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Berlin 6 October 1998 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Executive Committee Meeting Berlin, 7-9 October 1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- ITGLWF Strategic Approaches Subcommittee Berlin, October 1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Bruges, Belgium 12 May 1997 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Brussels 15 April 1998 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting Montreal, 15-17 October 1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Montreal 14 October, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- ITGLWF 7th World Congress Melbourne 15-19 April 1996 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- ITGLWF Presidium Meeting Bruges, Belgium 12 May 1997 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting Caracas, 28-30 October 1990 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Subscriptions, 1998-2000 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Companies, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Labeling Systems, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Clinton Administration/ Democratic Party, 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Japan Institute of Labour (JIL), 1997 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- JIL Program -- 1999 M. Chen, R. Jordan, A. Dacosta (Box 23, Folder 6)
- JIL Program - 1997 Katie Quin and Paul Filson (Box 23, Folder 7)
- JIL Program - 1995 Warren Pepicelli/ Joe Buonodonna (Box 23, Folder 8)
- FITTVCC/ORI Correspondence 1995 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Newspapers Received from AIFLD Columbia, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO 1996 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- International Trade Secretariats, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO International Affairs Dept. Resolutions, Speeches, etc., 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Center for International Labor Solidarity (AFL-CIO), 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO European Office (Paris), 1996-2000 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO International Affairs Department, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO International Affairs Committee, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO Working Women's Dept., 1996 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- AAFLI, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- AALC, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Free Trade Union Institute, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- AIFLD, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO's Polices International Affairs, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- ICFTU Circulars 1997 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- ILO Tripartite Meeting on the Globalization of the Footwear, Textile, and Clothing Industries, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Italian-American Labor Council, 1998-2000 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Jamaica, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Japan, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Jordan, 1995-2000 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Kazakhstan, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Kenya, 1995-2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Korea -- Strike re New Labor Laws (December 1996-1997) (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Republic of Korea, 1996-1999 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Kuwait, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Laos, 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Lebanon, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Lesotho, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Liberia, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Lithuania (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Mali, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Malawi, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Malaysia, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- FITTVCC Women's Committee Conference - March 1996 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- FITTVCC/ORI World Congress Mexico -- October 21-23, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Central American Organizing Seminar D.R., March 1998 --- Documents (Box 24, Folder 16)
- FITTVCC Organizing Seminar Santo Domingo, D.R. -- March 16-20, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- FITTVCC Executive Committee Meeting San Jose, Costa Rica -- Nov. 9-10, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- FITTVCC Executive Committee San Jose, Costa Rica -- Nov. 9-10, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- FITTVCC/ORI Executive Council & Committee Meetings - July 10-14 1995 Carcas, Venezuela (Box 24, Folder 20)
- ITGLWF News Africa, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- ITGLWF News Asia, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- ITGLWF 7th World Congress Melbourne, Australia, April 15-19 1996 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- ITGLWF Presidium & Exec. Comm. Meetings - Copenhagen, October 1995 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- India, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Ireland, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Israel, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Italy, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Federal Republic of Germany, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Greece, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Uzbekistan, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- United Kingdom, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Venezuela, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- United Kingdom, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Republic of Philippines, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Poland, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Senegal, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Singapore, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Spain, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- FITTVCC Correspondence 1996 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- FITTVCC Correspondence - 1995 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Denmark, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- DR, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Ecuador, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- The Netherlands, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Panama, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Pakistan, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Niger, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Mexico, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- FITTVCC, Constitution, 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  2 Floppy Discs
- ITGLWF 7th World Congress Melbourne, Australia, April 15-19, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- U.S. Legislation -- New and Pending, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- U.S. Prison Labor, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Works Councils, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- European Union, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- GATT/MFA (General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade/Multi Fibre Arrangement), 1977-1995 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Albania, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Argentina, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Australia, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Bangladesh, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Burkina Faso, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Chile, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Caribbean Regional, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- AALC Union-to-Union, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Jamaica, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Republic of Korea, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Memo to Finance -- 1992 General (Box 25, Folder 43)
- To: Jay Mazur, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Workers Rights [Folder 1 of 2], 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Transnational Corporations [Folder 1 of 3], 2000 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- South Africa - 1992 General (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Memos from ILGWU Staff Miscellaneous, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 48)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A Quito (Ecuador) y Lima (Peru), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A: San Pedro Sula (Honduras), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Relacion de Gastos Girqa A: Lima (Peru) y Bogota (Colombia), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A: New York, Sto. Domingo y San P. Sula, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Gira Del Secretario General FITTVCC/ORI Falda Cordova, Arg y Uruguay, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Gira Del Secretario General de FITTVCC/ORI A Republica Dominican y Puerto Rico, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Gira Del Secretario General de FITTVCC/ORI a Sao Paulo, Brasil, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Gira Del Secretario General de FITTVCC/ORI A Santo Domingo y Santiago de Rep. Dom., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Gira Del Secretario General de FITTVCC/ORI Miami-USA, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Relacion de Gastos de FITTVCC/ORI, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Gira Del Sec. Gral. FITTVCC/ORI San Jose, Costa Rica, C.A., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Gira Del Sec. Gral. FITTVCC/ORI Costa Rica, Honduras, Guatemala, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Gira Del Sec. Gral. FITTVCC/ORI Sao Paulo, Porto Alegre, Brasil, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Giral Del Sec. Gral. FITTVCC/ORI San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Gira Del Sec. Gral. FITTVCC/ORI Las Vegas, Nevada, U.S.A., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- XXIII Reunion del Comite Ejecutivo FITTVCC/ORI, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- FITTVCC/ORI Reunion Com. Ejec., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- XXIII Reunion del Comite Ejecutivo FITTVCC/ORI, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Temas de La XXII Reunion del Comite Ejecutivo de FITTVCC/ORI, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Relacion de Gastos 1-30 Nov/93 Gastos Costeados con Programa Union to Union, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- FITTVCC/ORI Relacion de Gastos, Diciembre, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- FITTVCC/ORI Relacion de Gastos, Nov./ 1993 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- FITTVCC/ORI Relacion de Gastos Mes Oct./ 93, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- FITTVCC/ORI Relacion de Gastos, Sept./ 1993 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- FITTVCC/ORI Relqacion de Gastos, Agosto/93, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- FITTVCC/ORI Relacion de Gastos Julio/93, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Balances Mes de Junio, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Balances Mes de Mayo, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Balances Mes de Abril, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Relacion de Gastos Del Banco de Los Trabajadores de Venezuela, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Balances Mes de Enero 1993 FITTVCC/ORI (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Balances Mes de Febrero 1993 FITTVCC/ORI (Box 26, Folder 32)
- FITTVCC/ORI Money's Wires Sent, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Balances Mes de Marzo 1993 FITTVCC/ORI (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A Guatemala, Costa Rica, Panama y Republica Dominicana del 15 de Sept/91, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Relacion de Gastos de Gira A Peru Del 22 Al 26 de Julio, 1991 J. Ramirez (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Gira A Chile 91 del 02 al 08 Abril, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- J.R. Per Diem Ecy 91/10 al 15/03/91, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Copias de Documentos Enviados Por El Senor Jose Ramirez al Presidium de La Internacional, Trabajos mas Importantes de Oct/90 a Oct/92 Reportados en Praga, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Copias de Documentos Enviados por el Senor Jose Ramiarez al Presidium de la Internacional, Trabajos mas Importantes de Oct/90 a Oct/91 Reportados en Praga, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Gira del Sr. Jose Ramirez FITIVCC Caracas-Madrid- Santiago de Campostela - Caracas Durante el Periodo - del o8 Al 14 Abril de 1991 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Travels by Jose Ramirez, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Gira Del Sr. Jose Ramirez FITIVCC. Caracas-Madrid-Santiago de Campos-tela-Caracas Durante el Periodo Del 08 de Abril Al 14 de Abril 1991 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- FITCC/ORI Travel to Guatemala, El Salavador and Panama-Caracas. From: 30-05-92 To 21-06-92, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- Itinerary by Jose Ramirez Brasil - Texas/ Miami Caracas 01/30/1992 - 02/19/1992 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- Gira Del Secretario General FITTVCC/ORI Cartagena de Indias, Colombia, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Relacion de Gastos XXI Reunion C. Ejecutivo Quito, Ecuador Del 16-05 al 31-05-91, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- FITVCC/ORI Relacion de Gastos, Diciembre, 93, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- Affiliates of International FITTVCC/ORI, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- FITTVCC/ORI Record of New Affiliates, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- Loan Payments Jose Ramirez, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 51)
- FITTVCC-ORI Guillermo Viracacha's Documents, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 52)
- FITTVCC/ORI Women's Conferences, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 53)
- The Women's Bureau: A Voice for Working Women, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 54)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances, Feb./94, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 55)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances January 1994 (Box 26, Folder 56)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances, March, 94, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 57)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira a Taipei, Taiwan (China) Del 04 Al 11 de Noviembre 1994 (Box 26, Folder 58)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira a Santiago (Chile) Del 21 Septiembre al 05 Octubre 1994 (Box 26, Folder 59)
- FITITVC Executive Committee Caracas 14-15 April 1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Central America, 1985-1995 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  Spanish, English
- ITGLWF Executive Committee Meeting Caracas, 28-30 October 1990 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- FITTVCC/ORI Exec. Bd. Com. Meet., 1995 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- FITTVCC/ORI Reports to AIFLD, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Haiti Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- FITTVCC/ORI Exec. Board Meeting Reports, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- FITTVCC/ORI Reports and Others Olga Diaz / Spain., 1994 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances May-June 1995 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- FITTVCC/ORI Federal Express Copies of Int. Air Waybill, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- FITTVCC International Brusselss, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances, December, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances, November, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances, October, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances, July, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances, August, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances, September, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- AIFLD/FITTVCC/ORI Programs, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- AIFLD/FITTVCC/ORI programs, 1993 2 of 2 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- FITTVCC Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- FITTVCC/ORI Correspondence #1 1993 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- AIFLD/Program 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Gira Del Secretario General FITTVCC/ORI Brusela, Belgica, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Gira Del Secretario General FITTVCC/ORI San Salvador, Sao Paulo, Brasil, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Gira Del Secretario General FITTVCC/ORI Capetown, Surafrica - New York, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Faxed Sent to FITVCC/ORI 1992 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Faxed Sent Various to the AIFLD, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- ITGIWF International Congress, Portugal 1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- DFITTVCC/ORI Women's Seminar 3/94 Documents sent to Participants and Others, (Books, Newspapers, etc.), 1994 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Reporte de Auditoria a FITTVCC, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Faxed Sent to the FITITVC Year 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Money's Wires Sent to FITTVCC 1989-1993 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- FITTVCC/ORI Fax Sent to Ramirez Programs Confirmation, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Faxed Sent to Neil Kearney, 1989-1992 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Faxs Sent to AIFLD/93, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- FITTVCC/ORI Exec. Board Meeting Argentina April, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- FITTVCC/ORI Congress, Chile, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Papers, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- FITTVCC/ORI Faxs Sent, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- FITTVCC/ORI, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- FITTVCC/ORI Women's Seminar Mexico D.F., 1994 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Faxed Sent to the FITITVC Year 1991 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- FITTVCC/ORI Women's Seminar Correspondence sent to Participants to the Seminar, Mexico D.F., 1994 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- FITTVCC/ORI Correspondence 1981-1988 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- FITTVCC/ORI Women's Seminar Questionnaires received from Participants FITTVCC, Mex. D.F., 1994 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Women's Seminar Travel Information, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Relacion de Gastos Gra a Bogota-Medellin (Colombia) Del 15 Al 19 De Febrero de 1994 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A New York, (U.S.A.) Del 24 Al 26 de Enero, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A Panama City, (Panama) del 15 Al 19 de Marzo, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A Cuidad de Mexico (Mexico) Del 4 Al 10 de Marzo, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A Buenos Aires (Argentina) del 05 Al 15 de Abril de 1994 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A New York (U.S.A.) Del 06 Al 07 de Julio de 1994 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Relacion de Gastos Gira A Lima (Peru)/ Santiago (Chile), 1994 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances, April, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- FITTVCC/ORI Balances, May, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- FITTVCC-ORI Bank Information 1995 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- FITTVCC-ORI Bank Information 1995 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- FITTVCC/ORI Women's Seminar 3/94 Correspondence Received From Participants, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- FITTVCC/ORI Correspondence #1 1995 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- FITTVCC/ORI 1994 #1 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Newspapers Received from AIELD Colombia, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- FITTVCC/ORI Money Wires for Programs, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 16)